CV

Pawel Pelech

Telephone: 0892252029
E-mail: pawelpelech@gmail.com

I have over five years of customer service experience. I have worked in multiple countries, on two continents in multinational environments. I am seeking a position that helps me utilize my skills and abilities and provides an environment where I can learn and progress.

EMPLOYMENT

July 2016 till present

Position

Stryker Neurovascular

Product builder

Duties and responsibilities

- Production of stroke treatment products.
- Correct performance of production process in clean room operation
- Operate a variety of packaging machines, package, seal and label product to specifications.
- Performing packaging operations with 100% accuracy.
- Visual inspection of parts and product.
- Maintaining accurate records and report data on computerized system.

Feb 2015 –June 2016 Position Duties and responsibilities Starbucks Ltd., Cork, Ireland Trainee shift supervisor

Duties and responsibilities

- Running shift, staffing plan, cash flow.
- Check temperatures of freezers, refrigerators, or heating equipment to ensure proper functioning.
- Describe menu items to customers or suggest products that might appeal to them.
- Order, receive, or stock supplies or retail products.
- Prepare or serve hot or cold beverages, such as coffee, espresso drinks, blended coffees, or teas.

Nov 2014- Feb 2015 Yves Rocher Manufacturing (via Cregg Recruitment)

Position General Operative

Duties and responsibilities

- Assembly on production line
- Quality control
- Maintenance of equipment
- Cleaning of all work surfaces in the controlled environment

June 2014 Nov 2014 CMC Landscapes, Cork, Ireland Position Landscape gardener

Duties and responsibilities

- Maintenance
- Operating plant and equipment
- Customer service

April 2013 June 2014 Fox and Ferret, Christchurch, New Zealand

Waiter

Position

Duties and responsibilities

- Customer service
- Bar cleaning
- Deliveries
- Orders

May 2012-Sept.2012 Wo Position Wa

Wolfes Irish Artisan Bistro, Dublin, Ireland Waiter, Kitchen Assistant

Duties and responsibilities

- Customer service
- Updating company's social media website
- Ordering stock

Aug 2008- Oct 2011 Acrobat catering Ltd. Dublin, Ireland

Position Bar assistant

Duties and responsibilities

- Customer service
- Ensuring food preparation areas were clean and hygienic
- Washing utensils and dishes and making sure they were stored appropriately
- Washing, peeling, chopping, cutting and cooking foodstuffs and preparing salads
- Cleaning the food preparation equipment, floors and other kitchen tools or areas

Nov. 2006- July 2007 Clarion Hotel, I.F.S.C., Dublin, Ireland Position Store/ Accommodation Assistant

Duties and responsibilities

- Performing all duties to provide excellent guest service in an efficient manner
- Responsible for receiving, storing, issuing, transferring or returning items that are used
- Producing, distributing and filling all necessary documents to support the receiving
- storing, transferring or returning of items used
- Rotating product in all areas to represent a First In, First Out philosophy of product usage
- Developing and maintaining positive communication and teamwork with all co-workers and Supervisors: Front-of-the house, Back of-the-house, Warehouse

Feb2004 - Sept. 2006 Amar -Trade Company, Zgorzelec, Poland Position Assembly operative

Duties and responsibilities

- Manufacturing of TV components
- Quality control
- Stocking shelves with merchandise
- Keeping the store tidy and clean including hovering and mopping
- Receiving and storing the delivery of large amounts of stock

TRAINING AND CERTIFICATION

First Aid Course Site Safe training Driving licence B Safe pass

Manual handling certificate HACCP level 1 certificate Scissor lift operator Licensed skydiver

EDUCATION

2014 Cork College of Commerce- Auto CAD course

2004 Technical Secondary School, Zgorzelec, Poland-Car mechanic

SKILLS

Polish language- native English language- fluent MS Office – advanced

INTERESTS

Climbing, Parachute Jumping, history